{
    "id": "bcc9cde974054aed9add7071f927ddfc",
    "title": "Who, Which, Whom, What, Whose, That",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "0be1f014b2dd45249306c5229445b328",
            "title": "Who, Whom, Which, Whose, That, What",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "……………… she said made me angry.",
                    "description": "What means ‘the things which’.",
                    "answers": [
                        "That",
                        "What",
                        "Which"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "She has acted in a movie …………….. name I don’t remember.",
                    "description": "Whose name means the same as ‘the name of which’.",
                    "answers": [
                        "which",
                        "what",
                        "whose"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "The only thing ………………. keeps me awake is tea.",
                    "description": "'What' means the things which. It cannot replace that. 'Which' is not common after 'only'.",
                    "answers": [
                        "that",
                        "what",
                        "which"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I have got something ………………. belongs to you.",
                    "description": "After quantifiers like something, anything and everything, we prefer that to which.",
                    "answers": [
                        "which",
                        "that",
                        "what"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "She married a nice young guy …………….. was her senior at college.",
                    "description": "The relative pronoun who replaces words like he, she or they.",
                    "answers": [
                        "who",
                        "whom",
                        "which"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "This is the house ………………",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "where I was born",
                        "that I was born in",
                        "in which I was born",
                        "All of the above"
                    ],
                    "correct": 3
                },
                {
                    "question": "It is a story ……………… will captivate readers of all ages.",
                    "description": "The relative pronoun which can only refer to things. That can refer to both people and things. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "that",
                        "which",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "The proposal ……………… she put forward was quite interesting.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "that",
                        "which",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "She is somebody ………………. really can’t stand.",
                    "description": "When the relative pronoun is the object of the relative clause, it is sometimes left out.",
                    "answers": [
                        "I",
                        "that I",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "She has married someone ……………. I really admire.",
                    "description": "Who is possible here in an informal style.",
                    "answers": [
                        "who",
                        "whom",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the name of the tall girl ………………. just walked in?",
                    "description": "In identifying relative clauses, we can use that to refer to people. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "who",
                        "that",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "Is that your car ……………….. is parked outside?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "that",
                        "which",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}